Scared Shrekless is a animation, comedy, family film directed by Gary Trousdale.
Shrek challenges Donkey, Puss in Boots and his other fairy tale character friends to spend the night in Lord
Farquaad's haunted castle, telling scary stories to see who can resist becoming scared and stay the longest.
Shrek (voice), played by Mike Myers.
Princess Fiona (voice), played by Cameron Diaz.
Puss in Boots (voice), played by Antonio Banderas.
Donkey (voice), played by Dean Edwards.
Gingerbread Man / Muffin Man (voice), played by Conrad Vernon.
Sugar (voice), played by Kristen Schaal.
Scared Shrekless is a 2010 American animated Halloween horror
comedy television special based on the Shrek franchise.
The special premiered on the American television
network NBC on October 28, 2010.
The special marks the first time outside of the video games that Donkey is now
voiced by Dean Edwards since Eddie Murphy was unable to return.
Rupert Everett and Chris Miller were both replaced by Sean Bishop as Prince Charming and Mister Geppetto respectively
while Miles Christopher Bakshi and Nina Zoe Bakshi reprise their roles as Fergus, Farkle, and Felicia.
It was produced with the working title of Shrek or Treat.
The film explores themes of halloween, haunted castle, scary stories.
The tone is lighthearted.